/*************************************************
**
** You're viewing a file in the SMAPI mod dump, which contains a copy of every open-source SMAPI mod
** for queries and analysis.
**
** This is *not* the original file, and not necessarily the latest version.
** Source repository: https://github.com/poohnhi/PoohCore
**
*************************************************/

{
    "Changes": [
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Andy"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Andy loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Friends George, Morris, Susan
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{AndyFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Apples"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Apples loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Friends Krobus
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random: Krobus, Krobus}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            },
            "When": {
                "ApplesHere": "true"
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Claire"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Claire loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Friends Martin
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random: Martin, Martin}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["GuntherSilvian"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:GuntherSilvian loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Friends Clint, Gus, Lewis, Penny, Willy, MarlonFay
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random: Clint, Gus, Lewis, Penny, Willy, MarlonFay}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Lance"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Lance loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Friends Marlon
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random: MarlonFay, MarlonFay}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            },
            "When": {
                "HasSeenEvent": "6951319"
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["MarlonFay"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:MarlonFay loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Friends Wizard Krobus Lance
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{MarlonFayFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Martin"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Martin loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Friends Claire
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Claire loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Morgan"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Morgan loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Friends Wizard, Jas, Vincent
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random: Wizard, Jas, Vincent}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            },
            "When": {
                "HasSeenEvent": "5978924"
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["MorrisTod"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:MorrisTod loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Friends Andy
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Andy loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            },
            "When": {
                "HasSeenEvent |contains=191393": "false"
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Olivia"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:MorrisTod loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Friends Jodi Caroline Pierre // Victor surprisingly doesn't have the family field hmmm
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:Jodi, Caroline, Pierre, Victor}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Scarlett"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Scarlett loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Friends Sophia
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Sophia loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            },
            "When": {
                "HasSeenEvent |contains=3691371": "true"
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Sophia"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Sophia loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Friends Sophia
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{SophiaFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Susan"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Susan loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Friends Andy, Lewis, Robin
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random: Andy, Lewis, Robin}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Victor"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Victor loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // He doesn't have FriendsAndFamily data... So no mother dialogue for now
                // Friends Sophia, Abigail, Sam, Sebastian
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random: Sophia, Abigail, Sam, Sebastian}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            }
        },
    ]
}